Dependency Inversion Principle (DIP)
	"Principle" used in architecting software.

Inversion of Control (IoC)
	Specific "pattern" used to invert interfaces, flow and dependencies.

Dependency Injection (DI)
	"Implementation" of IoC to invert dependencies.

Inversion of Control Container
	Framework to do dependency injection.

Yazılım dünyasında bu üç öğe birbirine karıştırılıyor, birbirleri için kullanılıyor. Üçü sanki aynı şeyi işaret ediyormuş, aynı anlama geliyormuş gibi düşünülüyor. Fakat bu yanlış.